Time to run with the big dogs!
Arctic Dogs is a animation, adventure, comedy film directed by Aaron Woodley.
Animals band together to save the day when the evil Otto Von Walrus hatches a
sinister scheme to accelerate global warming and melt the Arctic Circle.
Lemmy (voice), played by James Franco.
Swifty (voice), played by Jeremy Renner.
PB (voice), played by Alec Baldwin.
Magda (voice), played by Anjelica Huston.
Duke (voice), played by Michael Madsen.
Jade / Bertha (voice), played by Heidi Klum.
Arctic Dogs (also known as Arctic Justice internationally or Polar Squad in the UK) is a 2019 animated
comedy film co-written and directed by Aaron Woodley and co-directed by Dimos Vrysellas.
The film stars the voices of Jeremy Renner, Heidi Klum, James Franco, John Cleese, Omar
Sy, Michael Madsen, Laurie Holden, Anjelica Huston and Alec Baldwin.
The film centers around an arctic fox delivery worker as he and his cohorts
attempt to stop a walrus from attempting to melt the ice caps.
Entertainment Studios released Arctic Dogs on November 1,
2019, in Canada and the United States.
The film was a major critical and commercial failure, grossing less
than a fifth of its production budget of $50 million.
Critics panned the film's lack of originality,
humor, story, and animation quality.
Despite its reception, the film spawned a franchise, including a
web series and multiple spin-off series and films.
The tone is lighthearted.